nayadigantajobs.com 2019-06-08

# Nayadiganta Jobs Portal

###  Privacy Policy

Naya Diganta Jobs, sister concern of Daily Naya Diganta is the the true career portal in Bangladesh. nayadigantajobs.com collects information about jobs. We provide this job information for the readers.  

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for nayadigantajobs.com. This Privacy Policy governs the use and collection of information collected from you on the Naya Diganta Jobs site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information you may provide to us offline or through any means other than Naya Diganta Jobs site, other than as specifically identified below. For example, this Privacy Policy does not apply to information you may have provided when obtaining a home delivery subscription offline or when entering a sweepstakes by mail, fax or email. As used herein, "we," "us" and "our" refers to Naya Diganta Jobs site.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time and from time to time; the date of the most recent revision will appear on this page so check back periodically. You agree that your use of Naya Diganta Jobs site is subject to this Privacy Policy as then in effect. Continued access to the Naya Diganta Jobs site by you following any modification in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of this Privacy Policy as modified.

If you do not agree to be bound by all of the terms set forth below, do not use the Naya Diganta Jobs site.

Your Consent to This Privacy Policy

Your access to and use of this Website is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using our Website, or providing information to us, you agree and consent to our collection, use, disclosure, processing, transfer and use of information for the purposes set forth in this Policy, including but not limited to the transfer of your Personal Information between our Service Providers, affiliates and subsidiaries in accordance with this Policy. Any access to such information will be limited to the purpose for which such information was provided to our affiliate, subsidiary or Service Provider.

This Website may contain links to Web sites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties in the Bangladesh or elsewhere. This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected on any third-party Website. In most cases, third-party Websites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information about yourself. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Website.

Third Parties

The Naya Diganta Jobs site does not share e-mail and postal mailing lists with any other organizations in addition to those expressly stated herein. The Naya Diganta Jobs site does not sell or rent telephone numbers, e-mail addresses or fax numbers of registered users or others who communicate contact information to it or whose contact information has been otherwise obtained by The Naya Diganta Jobs site.

Third-Party Tracking Technologies

nayadigantajobs.com uses the Google Analytics tracking technology to track visits to our website. It allows us to analyze the usage of our website and is merely for our internal use.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web website. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your web experience. Your IP address might be used to track your location to provide you with various location based services and for our data analysis purposes. We may also analyze information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistics.

Security

We use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, and physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure.

Government and Legal Disclosures

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect through this Website, when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena), to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements that govern your use of this Website, or to protect the rights, property or safety of The Naya Diganta Jobs site, our members or others.

Revision and updates

nayadigantajobs.com regularly revises and updates its privacy policy and publishes changes to the policy at our website. This Privacy Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on this Website. For example, certain pages of this Website contain privacy notices providing details about the personal information we collect on those pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information.

Questions  
If at any time you believe the Naya Diganta Jobs Sites have not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to jobsnayadiganta@gmail.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

If you have any more questions about this policy please email us at jobsnayadiganta@gmail.com.
